<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

   <string-array name="electric_pallet_jack_inspection_data_list">
        <item>Is there excessive oil or water on the forks? Are they cracked or bent or worn?</item>
        <item>Are there large cuts that go around the circumference of the tire?</item>
        <item>Are there large pieces of rubber missing or separated from the rim?</item>
        <item>Is there bond separation on the tires that may cause slippage?</item>
        <item>Are there missing lugs?</item>
        <item>Are the cell caps and terminal covers on the battery in place?</item>
        <item>Are the battery\'s cables missing insulation?</item>
        <item>Is there an adequate amount of hydraulic fluid?</item>
        <item>Are all of the gauges working properly working?</item>
        <item>Has the steering been compromised in any way?</item>
        <item>If power steering: Is it working?</item>
        <item>Does the horn work?</item>
        <item>Is there hesitation when hoisting or lowering the forks?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="forklift_inspection_data_list">
        <item>Overhead Guard - Are there broken welds, missing bolts, or damaged areas?</item>
        <item>Hydraulic Cylinders - Is there leakage or damage on the lift, tilt,
            and attachment functions of the cylinders?</item>
        <item>Mast Assembly - Are there broken welds, cracked or bent areas, and worn or missing
            stops?</item>
        <item>Is there squeaking? Is there wear or damage or kinks, signs of rust, or any sign that
            lubrication is required on the lift chains or rollers?</item>
        <item>Is there excessive oil or water on the forks? Are they cracked or bent , worn, or
            mismatched?</item>
        <item>Are there large cuts that go around the circumference of the tire?</item>
        <item>Are there large pieces of rubber missing or separated from the rim?</item>
        <item>Is there bond separation on the tires that may cause slippage?</item>
        <item>Are there missing lugs?</item>
        <item>Are the cell caps and terminal covers on the battery in place?</item>
        <item>Are the battery\'s cables missing insulation?</item>
        <item>Is there an adequate amount of hydraulic fluid?</item>
        <item>Are all of the gauges working properly working?</item>
        <item>Has the steering been compromised in any way?</item>
        <item>If power steering: Is it working?</item>
        <item>If pedal goes all the way to the floor when you apply the service brake, that is
        the first indicator that the brakes are bad. Brakes should work in reverse, also.</item>
        <item>Does the parking brake work? The truck should not be capable of movement when the
        parking brake is engaged.</item>
        <item>If equipped with lights, are they working properly?</item>
        <item>Does the horn work?</item>
        <item>If the truck is equipped with a safety seat is it working?</item>
        <item>Is there hesitation when hoisting or lowering the forks, when using the forward or
        backward tilt, or the lateral travel on the side shift?</item>
        <item>Is there excessive oil on the cylinders?</item>
        <item>Is the tank guard bracket properly positioned and locked down?</item>
        <item>Is the propane hose damaged? It should not be frayed, pinched, kinked, or bound in
        any way.</item>
        <item>Is the propane hose connector threaded on squarely and tightly?</item>
        <item>Propane Odor - If you detect the presence of propane gas odor, turn off the tank
        valve and report the problem.</item>
        <item>Is there an adequate amount of oil in the engine?</item>
        <item>Engine Coolant - Visually check the level. Note: Never remove the radiator cap to
        check the coolant level when the engine is running or while the engine is hot. Stand to
        the side and turn your face away. Always use a glove or rag to protect your hand.</item>
        <item>Transmission Fluid - Check levels?</item>
        <item>Windshield Wipers - Do they work properly?</item>
        <item>Seat Belts - Do they work?</item>
        <item>Safety Switch - (found on stand up riding tow tractors) Is it working?</item>
        <item>Hand guards - (found on stand up riding tow tractors, walking pallet trucks,
        walking transtackers) Are they in place?</item>
        <item>Does the tow hook engage and release smoothly?</item>
        <item>Does the safety on the tow hitch catch work properly?</item>
        <item>Control Lever - Does the lever operate properly?</item>
        <item>Safety Interlock - (found on order pickers) If the gate is open, does the vehicle run?</item>
        <item>Gripper Jaws - (found on order pickers) Do the jaws open and close quickly and smoothly?</item>
        <item>Work Platform - (found on order pickers) Does the platform raise and lower smoothly?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="department_titles">
        <item>GROCERY</item>
        <item>PRODUCE</item>
        <item>DAIRY</item>
        <item>MEAT</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="role_titles">
        <item>ORDER PICKER</item>
        <item>REPLENISHER</item>
        <item>LOADER</item>
        <item>TRAINER</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>